<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome, to you future... on one-eyed-bat</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome, to you future... on one-eyed-bat</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Webscraper</title>
      <link>/blog/webscraper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/webscraper/</guid>
      <description>Overview: Developed a Python script for scraping job listings from Freelancer.com based on specific criteria, such as job titles containing &amp;ldquo;Web Scraping.&amp;rdquo; The script provides options for scraping single or multiple pages, allowing users to customize the data extraction process.
Key Features: Single Page Scraping: Extracts job details, including title, description, and required skills, from a single page on Freelancer.com.
Multiple Page Scraping: Enables users to scrape job listings from multiple pages, enhancing the scope of data collection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp Transcription app</title>
      <link>/blog/whisapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/whisapp/</guid>
      <description>Overview Developed a WhatsApp transcription application that serves as a translation service for deaf individuals. The application converts voice messages into text, allowing seamless communication between users, especially for those with hearing impairments.
Key Features: Utilizes WhatsApp Business API for message handling. Transcribes audio messages using OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s Whisper ASR model. Implements Flask for webhook handling and message delivery. Provides a user-friendly interface for easy communication.
How it Works : Receives incoming audio messages through the WhatsApp API.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
